http://www.hitachimed.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Hitachi Healthcare AmericaProductsMROasis 1.2TEchelon Oval 1.5TLegacy MRILegacy Open MRICTSCENARIA SE 128Supria True64Supria PlusSCENARIA VIEWUltrasoundProductsLISENDO 880 CardiologyProSound F37 Women's HealthProSound Alpha 7Noblus RadiologyARIETTA 70 Women's HealthARIETTA 60 CardiologyNoblus CardiologyARIETTA 70 CARDIOLOGYNoblus for Breast SurgeryARIETTA 70 SurgeryNoblus UrologyNoblus General ImagingNoblus Wound CareARIETTA 70 UrologyARIETTA 70 RadiologyProSound Alpha 7 ARIETTA 60 UrologyARIETTA 850 RadiologyARIETTA Precision SurgeryApplicationsWomen's HealthBreastGynecologyObstetricsPerinatologyReproductive MedicineRadiologyAbdominalBreast RadiologyInterventionalMusculoskeletalPediatric or NeonatalPelvicThyriodVascularSurgeryBreast surgeryGeneral SurgeryLaparoscopic SurgeryNeurosurgeryRobotic SurgerySurgical OncologyCardiologyAdultFetal/CongenitalPediatricsTEEVascular CardiologyUrologyAbdominal Imaging and BiopsyMRI Fusion Targeted BiopsyProstate Imaging and BiopsyScrotal and Penile DopplerSurgical and Robotic AssistedITVidiStar PlatformVidiStar ViewerVidiStar Structured ReportingHitachi Data AnalyticsDigital RadiologyDX-D 300DR 400DR 600DR 800Computed RadiographyDX-D 100DR RetrofitDX-D 600Particle therapyCompanyHitachi Healthcare AmericasTradeshows & EventsPress ReleasesBlogsCareersCustomer SupportHitachi Institute for MR TechnologistsDICOM & IHESecurity NoticesCustomer ServiceContactCustomer PortalMarketing SupportSelf Learning ModulesReference MaterialsArchitect SupportSign Up
Search
Global
Hitachi GroupProducts & Services
Hitachi GroupCorporate Information
Hitachi Healthcare America
Products
MROasis 1.2TEchelon Oval 1.5TLegacy MRILegacy Open MRICTSCENARIA VIEWSCENARIA SE 128Supria True64Supria PlusUltrasoundWomen's HealthRadiologySurgeryCardiologyUrologyITVidiStar PlatformVidiStar ViewerVidiStar Structured ReportingHitachi Data AnalyticsDigital RadiologyDR 400DX-D 100DX-D 300DX-D 600DR 600DR 800Computed RadiographyDR RetrofitParticle therapy
Company
Hitachi healthcare Americas
Learn about how Hitachi Healthcare technologies are helping clinicians around the world.
Tradeshows & Events
See our list of participating events.
Press Releases
View the latest in news.
Blogs
Get key information on the latest developments in value-based healthcare.
Careers
Join our team and see what we have to offer.
Customer Support
support services
Hitachi's support services provide unmatched benefits, while minimizing the total cost of ownership.
dicom & ihe
The most up to date versions of Hitachi's DICOM Conformance and IHE Statements.
security notices
Hitachi Healthcare risk assessments of the latest viruses, attacks and malware.
customer service
At Hitachi Healthcare, we make communicating with us easy.
Contact
Request Information
First Name
Last Name
Email
Phone
Country
- None -AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua & BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAscension IslandAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia & HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCanary IslandsCape VerdeCaribbean NetherlandsCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicCeuta & MelillaChadChileChinaChristmas IslandClipperton IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo - BrazzavilleCongo - KinshasaCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzechiaCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDiego GarciaDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatiniEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard & McDonald IslandsHondurasHong Kong SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKosovoKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao SAR ChinaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmar (Burma)NamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorth KoreaNorth MacedoniaNorwayOmanOutlying OceaniaPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoriesPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn IslandsPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaRwandaRéunionSamoaSan MarinoSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia & South Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSt. BarthélemySt. HelenaSt. Kitts & NevisSt. LuciaSt. MartinSt. Pierre & MiquelonSt. Vincent & GrenadinesSudanSurinameSvalbard & Jan MayenSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaSão Tomé & PríncipeTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad & TobagoTristan da CunhaTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks & Caicos IslandsTuvaluU.S. Outlying IslandsU.S. Virgin IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezuelaVietnamWallis & FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweÅland Islands
State
- None -AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
Zip Code
Company
City
Product Information
I am interested in purchasing a Hitachi product and would like more information.
MRI
Oasis 1.2TEchelon Oval 1.5TLegacy MRILegacy Open MRI
Ultrasound
LISENDO 880 CardiologyProSound F37 Women's HealthProSound Alpha 7Noblus RadiologyARIETTA 70 Women's HealthARIETTA 60 CardiologyNoblus CardiologyARIETTA 70 CARDIOLOGYNoblus for Breast SurgeryARIETTA 70 SurgeryNoblus UrologyNoblus General ImagingNoblus Wound CareARIETTA 70 UrologyARIETTA 70 RadiologyProSound Alpha 7 ARIETTA 60 UrologyARIETTA 850 RadiologyARIETTA Precision Surgery
Digital Radiology
DX-D 300DR 400DR 600DR 800Computed RadiographyDX-D 100DR RetrofitDX-D 600
CT
SCENARIA SE 128Supria True64Supria PlusSCENARIA VIEW
Information Technology
VidiStar PlatformVidiStar ViewerVidiStar Structured ReportingHitachi Data Analytics
For customer support issues, please call 1-800-800-3106 or visit our Customer Service page and submit the Email Contact form.
Customer Portal
Marketing Support
Self Learning Modules
Reference Materials
Architect Support
Accounts
Sign Up
Hitachi Healthcare America
PRIVACY POLICY
HITACHI HEALTHCARE AMERICAS CORPORATION PRIVACY POLICY
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING ANY PORTION OF THE HITACHI HEALTHCARE AMERICAS CORPORATION WEBSITE
Hitachi Healthcare Americas Corporation. (the "Company") has created this policy to protect your online privacy while you use its website. Please read this privacy policy in its entirety in order to understand all of the practices and procedures the Company follows relating to online privacy. This privacy policy may change from time to time, and any changes will be posted on this page so check back periodically to review any changes.
SCOPE
This privacy policy applies to the Company website,any mobile or other applications (collectively referred to herein as “website”), and to any personal information collected by the Company. It is designed to inform you of when, why, how and for what purpose the Company collects personal information from visitors to its websites. It is also designed to inform you about the types of information that is collected about you at the Company's websites. Finally, it is designed to inform you about our use of personal information collected at Company websites and to whom access to such personal information may be given. Our privacy policy is also designed to inform you about how you may access, amend, or delete personal information collected by the Company and how you may limit the Company's use of your personal information.
On occasion, the Company's websites are connected by "hyperlinks" to other companies' websites. Please note that the Company is not responsible in any way for the privacy practices of other websites and suggests that you review the privacy policies of those other companies' websites before using them.
Any third party with whom user data is shared (in compliance with this Policy) will provide the same or equal protection of user data as required by this Policy.
WHAT TYPES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES THE COMPANY COLLECT?
Generally, personal information includes a person's full name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and any other information that would allow someone to identify or contact you. While the Company does not collect personal information from you when you merely browse our websites, at the Company's websites, you may be asked to provide to the Company personal information in connection with the Company's online programs by filling out an online registration form. If you choose to register with the Company at its websites, some of the information that the Company may collect from you is public information which is readily available in public directories such as name, address and telephone number. Other types of information that the Company may collect from you is not currently found in publicly available directories such as your e-mail address. The types of personal information that the Company currently collects through an online registration form include: site name, your name, job title, street address, country, telephone number, fax number and e-mail address. Our server does not automatically record personal information. Such information can become known to the Company via its websites only when you voluntarily submit it. No information is collected without your express consent.
HOW DOES THE COMPANY USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
The Company stores personal information collected at its websites in a secure database. Personal information collected by the Company is used to fulfill your requests for information regarding the Company's products and services, and to contact you about the Company's products and services. When you provide personal information to the Company, you are asked to consent to the Company's use of your personal information as described in this privacy policy.
A few select employees at the Company have access to your personal information for monitoring, marketing, demographic, and promotional purposes as well as to assist us in customizing the content of our websites to provide information that may be of interest to you. Except as otherwise described in this privacy policy, the Company does not disclose personal information to any third parties. The Company may share your personal information with other companies when: (1) it is necessary to provide your personal information to another company that assists us in providing you products, services or information, (2) the Company is required to provide your personal information by law, court order or legal process, (3) the Company finds that your actions on one of its websites violates the Company's terms of use agreement to which you agree by using a Company website, or (4) the Company sells or otherwise transfers your personal information in connection to a successor of the Company or any subsidiary or division of the Company in connection with an asset sale, merger, consolidation, divestiture, stock sale or other corporate transaction, or by way of assignment (whether by operation of law or otherwise) in connection with any such or similar transaction or in connection with the administration of a bankruptcy estate.
WHAT ABOUT COOKIES?
Hitachi uses cookies*1 and Web beacons *2 to make it more convenient for you to use the site3, and to better inform you about our products and services.
A person can refuse to receive a cookie, or can display a warning message when receiving a cookie by changing the setting of a web browser. For more details, please see the instructions of the web browser you are using. Moreover, a person can reject a Web beacon by setting the browser to refuse the receipt of a cookie. Please note that by doing so you may not be able to use the all or part of the Company’s  website.
Glossary
*1 Cookies: Means information exchanged between a web server that controls a web site and a web browser that a person uses. Cookies may be saved as files in the disk of a person's PC. If you use a cookie, the web server can track and record information about which web pages the particular computer visits.
*2 Web Beacons: Mean technology that functions with a cookie to check how many times a person accesses a particular page.
However, neither Cookies of Web Beacons allow the Company to identify a person unless that person has entered their personal information while visiting the web site
OPTING-OUT
You may opt-out of having your personal information retained by the Company at any time, even after having granted the Company your consent to collect personal information by the Company by e-mail at info@hitachimed.com, informing the Company of your desire to opt-out, or by clicking on the hypertext link on the registration form located on the registration pages of our websites and following the opt-out instructions. Please note that in certain instances it still may be necessary to send you notices or other product even though you opted-out.
ACCESSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION ONCE GIVEN
You may inquire at any time about the accuracy and completeness of your personal information and its use and disclosure. Users of the Company’s website may update, amended, or correct any personal information, or request that the Company delete any personal information from the Company's database. To do so, simply e-mail the Company at info@hitachihealthcare.com, or write to the Company at 1959 Summit Commerce Park, Twinsburg, Ohio 44087, attention: Marketing Communications. On each e-mail you receive from the Company, you will be given the opportunity to change, modify or delete information which you have previously provided to the Company and you will also be given the opportunity to unsubscribe, thereby removing your e-mail address permanently from the Company's mailing list.
Footer
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Sitemap
© Hitachi Healthcare Americas 1995, 2020. All rights reserved.
W Pixel block
stackadapt pixel script
